All power. We welcome all people of the world to witness the first meeting of the Intercommunal Council of the Revolution, also known as the People's Council, or just the Council.
This is a formal public forum attributed and guided by the first people of the Turtle Island with representatives from various liberation and revolutionary groups, with the Black Panther Party as the host who completely and comprehensively reject the incumbent one world order currently controlled by the transnational capitalist class,
which upholds the destructive and predatory mechanism of the U.S. uniparty, Democrat and Republican, fascism, capitalism, racism, imperialism, nationalism, colonialism, and liberalism.
This body of representatives will serve as the interim temporary mechanism of the official deliberation for the people of the current class wartime until a full revolution from the current tyrannical system of capital is accomplished in a more suitable, decentralized representation of the people as established.
This body of intercommunal guardians of the people will also set the example and model for decentralized local, province, state, city, town, neighborhood councils of similar structure and representations to foster a cohesive momentum towards united sovereignty
In preparation for a full revolution from the incumbent one world order and to facilitate full freedom from the current enslaved world, the Council and all associated local formations of this Council will center the Four Winds Plan for United Sovereignty as a starting point of common strategy, deliberation, and coordination.
Each party represented to the Council will encourage their members to follow suit and conclusion within formal sessions and give viewers tangible tools and strategies to accomplish a hard revolution and bridge groups and cooperation for that goal while maintaining their own unique systems approach and sovereignty.
Sitting in solidarity before you and the intercommunal council are the following representatives and their representative party and our demographics.
The Black Panther Party represented by National Minister of Defense Bunchy Carter of the Tacoma Chapter.
The Panther Party formerly known as the White Panther Party represented by Central Committee Member Doc Molotov.
The Brown Beret represented by Capitana Esty of Southern California.
The Movement to Liberate Palestine represented by Mohams.
The American Indian Movement represented by myself.
The Rednecks Patriots and Veterans represented by Panther Party.
Member Mark Wayne.
The Panther's stance on indigenous sovereignty within colonialized land is unwavering in both ideology and practice.
Consequently, it is recognized by all represented parties that the intercommunal council is represented within Turtle Island and must be attributed by First Nations authority.
Therefore, the 10,000-plus-year-old position of the firekeeper will be revived in honor of the ancient traditions of deliberations within the Air Corps Confederacy.
Every session within the council will be open, closed, and attributed by the wisdom and direction of the firekeeper.
All officially recognized council, local and regional, operating under the model of the intercommunal council, must have a firekeeper, and all firekeepers must be from First Nations of Turtle Island.
This will maintain the safeguard that all deliberations for the revolution within Turtle Island will be represented and prioritize the sovereignty of First People of Turtle Island, and that no decisions concerning her future are made outside of her.
Honored to Fred Hampton, as host party of the intercommunal council, the Black Panther Party will always work to ensure that Fred Hampton's spirit of care and inclusion is observed by empowering the comrade parties and offering initial strategies of survival to be analyzed, adopted, or negotiated within its comrade parties.
First of all, I would like to state on behalf of the Black Panther Party, how much every person who is here is appreciated.
This is not for the weak of mind, of spirit, of physicality, of any kind.
So the fact that you're here says a lot.
There is a war that has been raging for quite some time, and it's intensifying right before our eyes.
The most important thing we can do now is find ways to unite instead of finding ways to stay divided.
There is a massive division movement happening right now.
I don't be on social media, so I don't see a lot of it, but I always end up seeing it, if you know what I mean.
This is the time when the truest definition of intercommunalism has to be enacted.
Under four winds is a good way to bring that into existence.
Much like we even created this council here, this council here, to make decisions and to find a way to move together down this road towards liberation,
we have to encourage those who are in our own communities to do the same.
We are not going to be in a position to make decisions for every person or every group of people.
These people have our greatest duty is actually to educate the people to the point where they make these decisions for themselves.
If they have a full understanding of exactly what it is they're facing, exactly what it is they're fighting,
exactly what it is they should be doing in order to bridge the gap and to close the doors
where some of the contradictions exist between themselves and the system.
At that point, we fundamentally change those people's relationship with their own oppression.
And that is when you can really start to walk people towards liberation.
Right now, I have to be very careful what I say.
But right now, there is absolutely an agenda that is being put into play against people much like ourselves.
The belief is that if we can keep them fighting about what's different, they'll never find what they have in common.
And as long as they don't find what they have in common, they'll never have power.
Well, this is us finding our commonality right here.
We all have our own specific fights on different fronts.
Black people have specific fights.
Our Native comrades have specific fights.
Our Redneck comrades have specific fights.
Our Latinx comrades have specific fights.
But we all have the same fight.
And until we recognize that, the division is going to ensure our defeat.
Division ensures our defeat.
But what does not, what works in our favor is this.
Finding what we have in common, learning the things that we can support one another on
and how we can learn from each other.
There are things that each of us can draw from each other's struggle.
There are things that Mark can teach me.
I can definitely learn a whole lot from Estee.
I'm quite sure.
Mohams, I'm sure I can learn a lot from you.
Dakota, I always learn a lot from you when I speak to you, whenever I see you.
Me and Gio have been learning from each other for the last five years.
Doc, I learn just how much I don't know every time I talk to you.
So, this is the time where we form the muscle that moves the Army forward.
We have to be the muscle, whether that muscle is on the front line or in the backside making decisions.
This is where we flex that muscle and where we learn how to flex them together.
You ever been in a situation where you're supposed to operate as a team?
I used to hate doing group projects in school because there's always one dummy.
They don't want to do what we're supposed to be doing.
In this, none of us can afford to be the dummy or we all die.
That's the difference here.
So, let's make sure that we are weighing every move that we make and every decision we make
with the actual weight of the seriousness of the situation in mind.
And as long as we do that, I think we'll be all right.
I'm looking forward to hearing everybody's thoughts and seeing what we can bring to the city.
All power to the people.
Power.
All power.